* [More  
        Business Processes =>](#)

Have a Question? \>>> [Ask](http://www.sankhya.com/comments.html)  
To Attend a Course \>>> [Register](https://www.edvantage.in/registration.html)  
Ready to Buy \>>> [Request Proposal](http://www.sankhya.com/sales/contact_sales.html)  
To Connect a Lead \>>> [Refer](http://www.sankhya.com/ReferALead.html)  

### Legal Terms and Privacy Policy

#### Terms and Conditions

PLEASE READ THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS CAREFULLY. BY USING THIS WEBSITE YOU INDICATE YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS. IF YOU DO NOT ACCEPT THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, THEN DO NOT USE THIS WEBSITE. THIS WEBSITE AND THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS ARE SUBJECT TO CHANGE AT ANY TIME WITHOUT NOTICE.

#### Use of Site

The materials contained on this website (such materials, include, but are not limited to, the design, layout, artwork and other elements of the website and any text, data, audio, software, logos, information, documentation, services or other materials contained on the website) are owned or licensed by Sankhya Technologies Private Limited ("SANKHYA") and are protected by copyright and trademark law, international treaties, and other intellectual property rights. You may view, download, print, and copy materials on this website for your own personal, informational and non-commercial use, provided that (i) you do not modify the materials, (ii) any copies that you may make must be marked "Copyright Sankhya Technologies Private Limited. All rights reserved." and (iii) you retain all copyright and proprietary notices originally contained in the materials on any copies. You may not use, display, reproduce, transmit, post or distribute any materials contained on this website for any commercial purpose. Nothing herein shall be construed as granting you any license or right to use this website or any materials contained on this website except as expressly provided herein.

#### Changes

Information on this web site may be changed or updated without notice. Sankhya may also make improvements and/or changes in the products and/or the programs described in this information at any time without notice.

#### Trademarks

SANKHYA, Varadhi, Web Varadhi, SANKHYA TECHNOLOGIES, SANKHYA Tools Collection, SANKHYA Translation Framework, Dynamically Targetable Tools Framework, SANKHYA Partners, SANKHYA Labs, SANKHYA Software, SANKHYA Assembler, SANKHYA Simulator, SANKHYA Development, SANKHYA Consulting, SANKHYA Education, SANKHYA Research, Varadhi Services, The Digital Bridge, AppChain, AppCore, AppBundle, AppFed are Trademarks, Service Marks or Registered Trademarks of Sankhya Technologies Private Limited. OMG and CORBA are either registered trademarks or trademarks of Object Management Group, Inc. in the United States and/or other countries. All other brands and names are the property of their respective owners.

#### No Warranty

Sankhya makes no warranties as to the accuracy or currency of the information or products contained on this web site. This website is available to all users "as is" without any representations or warranties of any kind, either express or implied, including warranties as to merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose. Sankhya makes no representations, warranties or undertakings that this website will be free from defects, including, but not limited to viruses and/or other harmful elements. This website may contain inaccuracies or typographical errors.

#### No Confidential Information

Sankhya does not want to receive confidential or proprietary information fro m you through this web site. Please note that any information or material sent to Sankhya will be deemed NOT to be confidential. By sending Sankhya any information or material, you grant Sankhya an unrestricted, irrevocable license to use, reproduce, display, perform, modify, transmit and distribute those materials or information, and you also agree that Sankhya is free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques that you send us for any purpose.

#### Product Plans

Information contained in this site may contain references to Sankhya's products, services or other programs that are not announced or available in all countries. Such references do not imply that Sankhya intends to announce such products, services or programs in any particular country. Sankhya's obligations with respect to its products and services are governed solely by the license agreements under which they are provided.

#### Links To Other Web Sites

Links to third party Web sites are provided solely as a convenience to you. Sankhya has not reviewed all of these third party sites and does not control and is not responsible for any of these sites or their content. Sankhya does not endorse or make any representations about them, or any information, software or other products or materials found there, or any results that may be obtained from using them. If you decide to access any of the third party sites linked to this Site, you do this entirely at your own risk.

#### Content Specific Advertisements

Some of the pages on this site include content specific advertisements supplied by Google or other organizations. Sankhya has not reviewed all of these third party sites and does not control and is not responsible for any of these sites or their content. Sankhya does not endorse or make any representations about them, or any information, software or other products or materials found there, or any results that may be obtained from using them. If you decide to access any of the third party sites linked to this Site, you do this entirely at your own risk.

#### Limitation of Liability

IN NO EVENT WILL SANKHYA BE LIABLE TO ANY PARTY FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL OR OTHER CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES FOR ANY USE OF THIS WEB SITE, OR ON ANY OTHER HYPER LINKED WEB SITE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY LOST PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF PROGRAMS OR OTHER DATA ON YOUR INFORMATION HANDLING SYSTEM OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF SANKHYA IS EXPRESSLY ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.

#### Privacy Policy

Sankhya Technologies has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following explains our information gathering and dissemination practices for www.sankhya.com.

#### Information Collected

In general, you can visit the SANKHYA website without providing personal information, but there are times when we will request personal information, such as contact and product requirements information. In some situations, you may be required to provide personal information in order to participate in our site's activities and offerings. Information is typically requested when you wish to download evaluation products, subscribe to online services, or when you are ordering products or services on our site.

We may also collect information when you visit our web site through the use of "cookie" technology, including web beacons and action tags.

When you submit personal information to Sankhya through its web site, you agree that your information may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed in any of the countries in which Sankhya and its affiliates are located.

#### How We Use the Information

We collect and use your information in order to give you better service, to provide you with convenient access to our products and services and to make our website more useful to you. The contact information we collect is used to deliver orders, information about our Company and partners and promotional material to you. It is also used to contact you when necessary. Cookies may be used for providing customized service.

SANKHYA will only disclose your personal information without notice when it believes disclosure to be required by law or regulation, or necessary to protect or defend the rights or property of SANKHYA, the safety of the public or the users of its site.

#### Choice/Opt-Out

When you provide us with your contact information, you may opt-out of receiving communications from us. You may also be removed from receiving email information about Sankhya at any time by sending an email with your name and email address to remove@sankhya.com.

#### Links to Other Sites

Sankhya's web sites may contain links to other sites whose privacy and information practices may be different than ours. You should consult the other sites' privacy notices. Sankhya is not responsible for the content or privacy policies of other sites.

#### Security

We use reasonable procedures to help safeguard the information we collect from you online. We urge you to take precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often and make sure you use a secure browser.

#### Corrections to Information/ Contacting the Web Site

If you would like to correct any information you have provided to us or if you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with our web site, you can contact the webmaster@sankhya.com.

This privacy policy is subject to change without notice.

### Quick Links

### Knowledge Hub

### Help Center

* **+91 94449 72818**

### Connect With Us

© Sankhya Technologies Private Limited [Legal Terms & Privacy Policy](http://www.sankhya.com/legal.html)  
Site Generated By [V-One CMS](https://www.hamara.in/index.html)
